<Language xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Code>EN</Code>
  <GameTip>
    <String>Press {KEY:HelmetSlot}, {KEY:SuitSlot}, {KEY:BackSlot}, {KEY:UniformSlot}, or {KEY:ToolBeltSlot} to toggle through interactions and slots on any slot item you're wearing. Press and hold to swap between that slot and your active hands.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:ToggleHandPower} or {KEY:SecondaryAction} to toggle what you're holding in your hands on or off.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:ToggleLight} to toggle your {THING:ItemSpaceHelmet} lights on or off quickly.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:EmoteWave} to make your character wave at other stationeers.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:Jetpack} to toggle your {THING:ItemSpacepack} propulsion on or off.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:ToggleUI} to toggle the User Interface on or off to get amazing screenshots or video.</String>
	<String>Pressing {KEY:Ascend} makes you ascend when your {THING:ItemSpacepack} is on. Toggle your {THING:ItemSpacepack} on/off with {KEY:Jetpack}.</String>
	<String>Pressing {KEY:Descend} will make you descend if your {THING:ItemSpacepack} is on. Toggle the {THING:ItemSpacepack} on/off using the {KEY:Jetpack} key.</String>
	<String>Press {KEY:InventorySelect} to swap between an open inventory slot and your active hand.</String>
	<String>Pressing {KEY:Drop} drops whatever's in your hand. Holding {KEY:Drop} throws it. Hold longer to throw further.</String>
	<String>Pressing {KEY:SwapHands} swaps what hand is active. Pressing {KEY:ActiveHandSlot} will cycle through the interaction options on whatever is in your active hand.</String>
	<String>Press {KEY:Internals} to quickly toggle your {THING:ItemSpaceHelmet} open or closed.</String>
	<String>Press {KEY:Chatting} to start chatting to other players.</String>
	<String>Press {KEY:RotateLeft} to rotate the construction cursor left, {KEY:RotateRight} to rotate right, {KEY:RotateUp} to rotate up, {KEY:RotateDown} to rotate down, {KEY:RotateRollLeft} to roll left, or {KEY:RotateRollRight} to roll right.</String>
	<String>Space isn't as empty as it sounds.</String>
	<String>Hold a {THING:ItemWeldingTorch} in one hand while turned on, and a stack of {THING:ItemIronSheets} in another in order to upgrade the build state of an {THING:StructureFrameIron}.</String>
	<String>Place a stack of {THING:ItemIronOre} in a powered {THING:StructureArcFurnace} in order to smelt it into an {THING:ItemIronIngot}.</String>
	<String>Place a {THING:MotherboardLogic} in a {THING:StructureComputer} to enable logic with an IC chip. You will be able to add conditions and actions that control the states of devices on the same data network.</String>
	<String>When altering the quantity of something via a button in world, hold down {KEY:QuantityModifier} while clicking to use smaller increments.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:ItemKitLogicInputOutput} to create a {THING:StructureLogicReader} or {THING:StructureLogicWriter}. Readers allow you to read values from other devices, writers allow you to change values on devices. When combined with Math Units, you can make extremely complex automated systems.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:ItemKitLogicInputOutput} to create a {THING:StructureLogicBatchReader} or {THING:StructureLogicBatchWriter}. Readers allow you to read values from an entire group of other devices, writers allow you to change values on entire groups of other devices.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:StructureRecycler} to convert things you no longer want into usable reagents. Pass the outputted {THING:ItemReagentMix} into a {THING:StructureCentrifuge} to convert it back into ore, ready for a {THING:StructureFurnace}.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:StructureHydraulicPipeBender} to manufacture atmospheric items, such as the {THING:ItemKitAtmospherics} which allows you to build useful machines such as the {THING:StructureAirConditioner} or {THING:StructureFiltration}.</String>
	<String>The more damaged your suit is, the less efficiently it will work. Duct tape can fix that.</String>
	<String>The more damaged your suit is, the less efficiently it will work.</String>
	<String>After the original Stationeers Handbook collapsed into a singularity, it was replaced by the Stationpedia. Press {KEY:Help} to open it for guidance in-game.</String>
	<String>Your starting {THING:ItemEvaSuit} and {THING:ItemSpaceHelmet} will catch on fire in a hot temperatures. Use {THING:ItemHardSuit} in dangerous environments.</String>
	<String>The Stationeers program was established by the Offworld Development Agency to support exploration of the Solar System, and beyond.</String>
	<String>Paying attention to your suit warnings. They can help prevent disaster.</String>
	<String>{THING:ItemHardBackpack} can carry more items, but can't carry you!</String>
	<String>The more damaged your suit is, the less efficiently it will work.</String>
	<String>If your station feels gloomy, lift your mood with tunes from the {THING:StructureKlaxon} or build your own sampler using logic.</String>
	<String>{THING:StructureHarvie} allows you to fully automate the planting, growing and harvesting of plants.</String>
	<String>The Extended Tooltips can be turned on/off in the Settings menu.</String>
	<String>You can clear all open windows on your screen at once by pressing {KEY:HideAllWindows}.</String>
	<String>{THING:ItemCrowbar} can be used to open unpowered doors and power controllers.</String>
	<String>{THING:ItemMiningDrill} can be changed to 'Flatten' mode to help you create flat floors when mining.</String>
	<String>The {THING:ItemWearLamp} can be used for illumination without wearing a helmet.</String>
	<String>By holding {KEY:MouseControl} you can enable your mouse cursor and drag items in and out of your inventory or between slots.</String>
	<String>The basic space helmet insulates Stationeers against everything from hard vacuum to weird cooking smells.</String>
	<String>Physics is your friend. Until it's not.</String>
	<String>The frictional adherence adjustor is a bi-rotational model with a columnated uni-grip. It's not just a screwdriver</String>
	<String>It's not actually 'milk', but an Agrizero-patented synthesis of {THING:ItemSoyOil} and {THING:ItemFern}, delicately blended in the {THING:ApplianceChemistryStation}.</String>
	<String>Illegal on Earth since the Chengdu Event, Norsec nuclear power cells found a new and drastically less safety-conscious market offworld.</String>
	<String>Hungry? Cereal bars are compact, nutritious, and refreshingly low on radiation.</String>
	<String>Sick of replacing normal filters?  Medium and Heavy filters last 5x and 20x as long, but are more expensive.</String>
  </GameTip>
</Language>