<Language xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Code>EN</Code>
  <GameTip>
    <String>Press {KEY:HelmetSlot}, {KEY:SuitSlot}, {KEY:BackSlot}, {KEY:UniformSlot}, or {KEY:ToolBeltSlot} to toggle through interactions and slots on any slot item you're wearing. Press and hold to swap between that slot and your active hands.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:ToggleHandPower} to toggle what you're holding in your hands on or off quickly.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:ToggleLight} to toggle your {THING:ItemSpaceHelmet} lights on or off quickly.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:EmoteWave} to make your character wave at other stationeers.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:Jetpack} to toggle your {THING:ItemSpacepack} propulsion on or off quickly.</String>
    <String>Press {KEY:ToggleUI} to toggle the User Interface on or off to get amazing screenshots or video.</String>
	<String>Pressing {KEY:Ascend} will make you ascend if your {THING:ItemSpacepack} is on, otherwise your character will try to jump. You can toggle the {THING:ItemSpacepack} on or off using the {KEY:Jetpack} key.</String>
	<String>Pressing {KEY:Descend} will make you descend if your {THING:ItemSpacepack} is on. You can toggle the {THING:ItemSpacepack} on or off using the {KEY:Jetpack} key.</String>
	<String>Press the {KEY:InventorySelect} key if you want to swap something between an open inventory slot and your active hand.</String>
	<String>Pressing and releasing the {KEY:Drop} key will make you immediately drop whatever is in your hands. If you hold the {KEY:Drop} key down, it will try to throw it. The longer you hold it, the further you will throw.</String>
	<String>Pressing {KEY:SwapHands} swaps what hand is active. Pressing {KEY:ActiveHandSlot} will cycle through the interaction options on whatever is in your active hand.</String>
	<String>Press {KEY:Internals} to quickly toggle your {THING:ItemSpaceHelmet} open or closed.</String>
	<String>Press {KEY:Chatting} to start chatting to other players. A small box will appear in the lower right of the screen with the text you write before sending.</String>
	<String>To change the orientation of your construction cursor, press {KEY:RotateLeft} to rotate left, {KEY:RotateRight} to rotate right, {KEY:RotateUp} to rotate up, {KEY:RotateDown} to rotate down, {KEY:RotateRollLeft} to roll left, or {KEY:RotateRollRight} to roll right.</String>
	<String>Want to know how to make something? Insert a {THING:CartridgeElectronicReader} into a {THING:ItemTablet} and turn it on with the {KEY:ToggleHandPower} key while it's in your active hand.</String>
	<String>Hold a {THING:ItemWeldingTorch} in one hand while turned on, and a stack of {THING:ItemIronSheets} in another in order to upgrade the build state of an {THING:StructureFrameIron}.</String>
	<String>Place a stack of {THING:ItemIronOre} in a powered {THING:StructureArcFurnace} in order to smelt it into an {THING:ItemIronIngot}.</String>
	<String>Place a {THING:MotherboardLogic} in a {THING:StructureComputer} to enable logic control. You will be able to add conditions and actions that control the states of devices on the same data network.</String>
	<String>When altering the quantity of something via a button in world, hold down {KEY:QuantityModifier} while clicking to use smaller increments.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:ItemKitLogicInputOutput} to create a {THING:StructureLogicReader} or {THING:StructureLogicWriter}. Readers allow you to read values from other devices, writers allow you to change values on devices. When combined with Math Units, you can make extremely complex automated systems.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:ItemKitLogicInputOutput} to create a {THING:StructureLogicBatchReader} or {THING:StructureLogicBatchWriter}. Readers allow you to read values from an entire group of other devices, writers allow you to change values on entire groups of other devices.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:ItemKitLogicInputOutput} to create a {THING:StructureLogicSlotReader} which allows you to read slot values from device with slots. Some devices allow you to get specialist slot information such as plant growth in the {THING:StructureHydroponicsStation}.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:StructureRecycler} to convert things you no longer want into usable reagents. Pass the outputted {THING:ItemReagentMix} into a {THING:StructureCentrifuge} to convert it back into ore, ready for a {THING:StructureFurnace}.</String>
	<String>Use a {THING:StructureHydraulicPipeBender} to manufacture atmospheric items, such as the {THING:ItemKitAtmospherics} which allows you to build useful machines such as the {THING:StructureAirConditioner} or {THING:StructureFiltration}.</String>
  </GameTip>
</Language>