<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Language xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
<Name>English</Name>
<Code>EN</Code>
<Font>font_english</Font>
    <Interface>
        <Record>
            <Key>06BasicAtmospherics</Key>
            <Value>Basic Atmospherics</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>BasicAtmosphericsDescription</Key>
            <Value>In this lesson you will learn how to fill a small base with breathable atmosphere.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>TheTabletTask1</Key>
            <Value>Open backpack using 4</Value>
        </Record>
         <Record>
            <Key>TheTabletTask2</Key>
            <Value>Grab the tablet from your backpack and put it in either hand.</Value>
        </Record>
         <Record>
            <Key>TheTabletTask2.5</Key>
            <Value>Insert tracker Cartridge</Value>
        </Record>
         <Record>
            <Key>TheTabletTask3</Key>
            <Value>Turn on the Tablet</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>TheTabletAtmoDescription</Key>
            <Value>Insert the Tracker Cartridge into the {THING:ItemTablet}.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>BasicAtmosphericsDescription</Key>
            <Value>In this lesson you will learn how to fill a small base with a breathable atmosphere.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Oxyie-Gen</Key>
            <Value>Gathering Oxite.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Oxyie-GenTask1</Key>
            <Value>You will need to mine around 80 oxite to pressurize the base. You can find a deposit near the tracking beacon. Scroll through the options until you find the correct beacon.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Oxyie-GenDescription</Key>
            <Value>Oxite is a frozen, breathable gas that exists in small deposits on most planets. Oxite will melt unless it's in your backpack or mining belt. 
        
Using the tablet, navigate to the Oxite site.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>AtmoAirLock</Key>
            <Value>Entering the Airlock</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>AtmoAirLockDescription</Key>
            <Value>An airlock is a device that permits the passage of people and objects between a pressurized base and its surroundings, while minimizing the change of pressure and loss of air from the base.

Currently the base has no internal atmosphere, so the airlock will not work correctly as it requires 100kpa to function. We can still enter the base by cancelling the pressurization cycle on the airlock. Remember this if your base has an air leak and you need to enter or exit it without running the cycle.</Value>
        </Record>
    <Record>
        <Key>AtmoAirLockTask1</Key>
        <Value>Enter the airlock and press the "Cycle to Interior" button on the console. Wait for the exterior door to close, and a new button labelled "Cancel Pressurize" will appear. Press this button and the internal door will open.
        </Value>
    </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>AtmosAnalyser</Key>
            <Value>Analysing Atmosphere.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>AtmosAnalyserDescription</Key>
            <Value>The Atmospheric Analyzer is used to analyse the composition, temperature and pressure of the current atmosphere.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>TheTabletTaskAtmo</Key>
            <Value>Insert the {THING:CartridgeAtmosAnalyser} into the {THING:ItemTablet}</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Creating_Atmo</Key>
            <Value>Generating an Atmosphere.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Creating_AtmoDescription</Key>
            <Value>The simplest way of creating a breathable atmosphere is to mine oxite, then drop it into your base and let it melt. This will release breathable oxygen into the atmosphere, and increase air pressure. Be careful when melting oxite as you could over-pressurize the base, causing damage to walls. Humans need to breathe a minimum 20% oxygen without pollutants or poisons. You can have a small amount of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere but exceeding 10% is not recommended.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Creating_AtmoTask1</Key>
            <Value>Turn the {THING:ItemTablet} on.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Creating_AtmoTask2</Key>
            <Value>Drop Oxite into the room and wait for it to melt. It will generate a breathable atmosphere, bringing the exterior pressure up to 60kPa.</Value>
        </Record>
        <Record>
            <Key>Creating_AtmoTask3</Key>
            <Value>Once the pressure has reached an acceptable safe level, open your helmet and take a breath of fresh, fresh air.</Value>
        </Record>
    </Interface>
</Language>