<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Language xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Name>English</Name>
  <Code>EN</Code>
  <Font>font_english</Font>
  <Interface>
  	<Record>
      <Key>EscapeFromMarsTitle</Key>
      <Value>Escape From Mars [BETA]</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>EscapeFromMarsDescription</Key>
      <Value>FOR TESTING: With only a meager amount of supplies, you must utilize your wits and spirit to find a way to survive on Mars.  All going to plan, this will ultimately lead to building a rocket that's capable of leaving Mars' atmosphere.</Value>
    </Record>
  	<!-- Mission Stage: In Case of Emergency -->
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTitleInCaseOfEmergency</Key>
      <Value>In Case of Emergency...</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsDescInCaseOfEmergency</Key>
      <Value>Your suit is damaged and you need to find some food.</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskGetTape</Key>
      <Value>Find some {THING:ItemDuctTape}</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskGetFood</Key>
      <Value>Find a {THING:ItemCerealBar}</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage1</Key>
      <Value>EMERGENCY GUIDE</Value>
    </Record> 	
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage1Page1</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 1 of 2\nDONT PANIC.\n\nIf you're reading this you've survived the evacuation - congratulations.  Regardless of your environment your first priority is to check the health of yourself and those around you.  Be sure to check suit integrity as well as there is no telling what environment you may find yourself in and protecting whatever air supply you have is crucial.</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage1Page2</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 2 of 2 \nIf you are near an intact escape pod and attached supply crate you should have some crucial supplies to aide your wait for rescue. If not, then search for survivors.  You should be sure to note the location of, or collect, any supplies that will be of upmost importance for your survival such as food, batteries, utility materials like duct tape and portable survival equipment. \n</Value>
    </Record> 

	<!-- Mission Stage: Aquire Raw Materials -->
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTitleRawMaterials</Key>
      <Value>Beg, Burrow and Steal</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage2</Key>
      <Value>RAW MATERIALS</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsDescRawMaterials</Key>
      <Value>Find a way to produce the basic materials you need to get manufacturing underway.</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskGetIronIngots</Key>
      <Value>Get a {THING:ItemIronIngot}</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskGetCopperIngots</Key>
      <Value>Get a {THING:ItemCopperIngot}</Value>
    </Record>
		<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskGetGoldIngots</Key>
      <Value>Get a {THING:ItemGoldIngot}</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage2Page1</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 1 of 5 \nBEG, BURROW or STEAL\n\nLuckily our manufacturing tools have knowledge of all the recipes you're likely to need in your situation.  Unfortunately, they'll need raw materials in order to do so.  These could come from several sources based on your situation:</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage2Page2</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 2 of 5 \nSCAVENGE\n\nIf your vessel is still largely intact, you may be able to find materials in their processed form, either already inside manufacturing machines or stored nearby.</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage2Page3</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 3 of 5 \nDISMANTLE\n\nIf you're able to find or manufacture an Angle Grinder, you should be able to use it to dismantle some of the ship wreckage.  A Recycler can be used to break these down into a mix of it's component materials and a Centrifuge will separate them out so they can be re-smelted into usable materials.</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage2Page4</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 4 of 5 \nEXCAVATE\n\nVery dependent on your surroundings, some exploratory vessels were equipped with basic mining equipment.  If you are lucky enough to find yourself somewhere with an abundance of mineral resources, this is certainly a viable option.</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage2Page5</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 5 of 5\nSMELT\n\nThe most straightforward way to convert raw materials into processed ingots ready for manufacturing is using the Arc Furnace and providing it with some power.  If you're limited on resources it should probably be your first investment, as if you cannot scavenge sufficient materials it'll be a requirement eventually to ensure you're able to produce more.</Value>
    </Record> 
	
	<!-- Mission Stage: Setup Manufacturing -->
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTitleSetupManufacturing</Key>
      <Value>Seizing the means of production</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage3</Key>
      <Value>PRODUCTION 101</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsDescSetupManufacturing</Key>
      <Value>In order to manufacture everything we'll need, we should start with a {THING:ItemKitHydraulicPipeBender} and a {THING:ItemKitElectronicsPrinter}.</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskManufactureHPB</Key>
      <Value>Manufacture a {THING:ItemKitHydraulicPipeBender}</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskManufactureEP</Key>
      <Value>Manufacture a {THING:ItemKitElectronicsPrinter}</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage3Page1</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 1 of 5\nMANUFACTURING \nWhile highly likely that rescue efforts are already underway, it may be some time before they're able to reach you.  It would be pertinent to plan for a longer stay.  You'll need to set up some basic manufacturing infrastructure.  An Autolathe is the natural starting point, and this will allow you to construct more task-specific crafting machines.</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage3Page2</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 2 of 5 \nPOWER TO THE PERSON \n\nHopefully by this point you've found some batteries, and some means to charge them.  The easiest way to supply power to a network is by connecting batteries to an Area Power Control unit.  To provide the power you'll need for Smelting and bulk manufacturing however, you'll need something a little more convenient.  The best way to handle this depends on your situation, but options include;</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage3Page3</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 3 of 5 \nSOLID FUEL GENERATOR \nThis will generate power by burning fossilized hydrocarbons in solid form.  The kit can be manufactured in an the Electronics Printer or a Fabricator.</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage3Page4</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 4 of 5 \nGAS GENERATOR \nThis will extract energy from the combustion resulting from igniting a hydrogen/oxygen fuel mix.  A Clean burn will result in a greater power output, but you'll need to carefully manage the amount of fuel being fed in and likely use a transformer to limit the power output or you'll suffer from overloaded cables.</Value>
    </Record> 
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage3Page5</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 5 of 5 \nSOLAR PANELS \nSolar Panels.  Once placed, you'll need to complete them by with a glass sheet - but once that's done they'll generate a nominal amount of power during the day.  You can use your wrench to adjust the vertical and horizontal angle to try face the sun but in the long term you might want to look at using a logic circuit and a daylight sensor to track it for you.</Value>
    </Record> 	
	
	
	<!-- Mission Stage: Food Supply -->
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTitleFoodSupply</Key>
      <Value>A Reliable Food Source</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage4</Key>
      <Value>GARDENING GUIDE</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsDescFoodSupply</Key>
      <Value>We don't know how long you'll need to survive here.  We should prepare a renewable source of food just in case.</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskPrepareAtmos</Key>
      <Value>Create a pressurized room with an atmosphere sufficient to grow Potatoes.</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTaskGrowPotato</Key>
      <Value>Grow a {THING:ItemPotato} to maturity.</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage4Page1</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 1 of 2 \nLITTLE GREEN THUMBS\nThe bare minimum you'll need to be able to grow crops is a Hydroponics Tray or Portable Hydroponics.  This will need to be supplied with a source of water and placed in an atmosphere of at least ~20kpa, around 20-25degrees Celcius and containing a small amount of carbon dioxide.</Value>
    </Record> 	
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTabletStage4Page2</Key>
      <Value>PAGE 2 of 2\nThe toughest requirement is obtaining some seeds to get started.  Each escape pod contains a supply crate with a nominal amount of seeds to get you started - protecting these is crucial.  If you became seperated from your escape pod, if you can find a tracking cartridge you may be able to use it to track the pods beacon.</Value>
    </Record> 	
	
	<!-- Mission Stage: Spawn Mothership & Engine -->
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsTitleCreateRocket</Key>
      <Value>Creating a Rocket</Value>
    </Record>
	<Record>
      <Key>MarsDescCreateRocket</Key>
      <Value>Create a Rocket by crafting a {THING:StructureLaunchPad} and attaching required modules to it.</Value>
    </Record>
  <Record>
    <Key>MarsTaskBuildLaunchPad</Key>
    <Value>Construct Rocket LaunchPad</Value>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Key>MarsTaskBuildEngine</Key>
    <Value>Construct Rocket Engine</Value>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Key>MarsTaskBuildFuelTank</Key>
    <Value>Construct Rocket FuelTank</Value>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Key>MarsTaskBuildCommand</Key>
    <Value>Construct Rocket Command module</Value>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Key>MarsTitleLaunchRocket</Key>
    <Value>Launching the rocket</Value>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Key>MarsDescLaunchRocket</Key>
    <Value>After fueling your newly constructed rocket, you can finally return to civilization.</Value>
  </Record>
  <Record>
    <Key>MarsTaskLaunchMothership</Key>
    <Value>Launch the rocket</Value>
  </Record>
  </Interface>
</Language>